It'll blow your mind.
Wedlock is a action, science fiction, thriller film directed by Lewis Teague.
A male prison escapee heads for his hidden loot,
electronically attached to a female prisoner.
Frank Warren, played by Rutger Hauer.
Tracy Riggs, played by Mimi Rogers.
Noelle, played by Joan Chen.
Sam, played by James Remar.
Warden Holliday, played by Stephen Tobolowsky.
Emerald, played by Basil Wallace.
Wedlock is a 1991 American science fiction-action television film from HBO Pictures, directed by
Lewis Teague and starring Rutger Hauer, Mimi Rogers, Joan Chen, and James Remar.
It received an Emmy Nomination for Sound Editing.
The film follows a diamond thief sent to a prison which uses new technology
linked explosive neck collars to keep its prisoners from escaping.
After learning who his collar is linked to, they escape, but the police
pursuing them and those who want the diamonds are a constant threat.
The film explores themes of future, prisoner, escape, explosive, heist.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.